<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="ACCESS_CHECKIN_PROPERTIES">Allows read/write access to the \"properties\" table in the checkin database, to change values that get uploaded.</string>
	<string name="ACCESS_COARSE_LOCATION">Allows an application to access coarse (e.g., Cell-ID, WiFi) location</string>
	<string name="ACCESS_FINE_LOCATION">Allows an application to access fine (e.g., GPS) location</string>
	<string name="ACCESS_LOCATION_EXTRA_COMMANDS">Allows an application to access extra location provider commands</string>
	<string name="ACCESS_MOCK_LOCATION">Allows an application to create mock location providers for testing</string>
	<string name="ACCESS_NETWORK_STATE">Allows applications to access information about networks</string>
	<string name="ACCESS_SURFACE_FLINGER">Allows an application to use SurfaceFlinger\'s low level features</string>
	<string name="ACCESS_WIFI_STATE">Allows applications to access information about Wi-Fi networks</string>
	<string name="ACCOUNT_MANAGER">Allows applications to call into AccountAuthenticators.</string>
	<string name="AUTHENTICATE_ACCOUNTS">Allows an application to act as an AccountAuthenticator for the AccountManager</string>
	<string name="BATTERY_STATS">Allows an application to collect battery statistics</string>
	<string name="BIND_APPWIDGET">Allows an application to tell the AppWidget service which application can access AppWidget\'s data.</string>
	<string name="BIND_DEVICE_ADMIN">Must be required by device administration receiver, to ensure that only the system can interact with it.</string>
	<string name="BIND_INPUT_METHOD">Must be required by an InputMethodService, to ensure that only the system can bind to it.</string>
	<string name="BIND_WALLPAPER">Must be required by a WallpaperService, to ensure that only the system can bind to it.</string>
	<string name="BLUETOOTH">Allows applications to connect to paired bluetooth devices</string>
	<string name="BLUETOOTH_ADMIN">Allows applications to discover and pair bluetooth devices</string>
	<string name="BRICK">Required to be able to disable the device (very dangerous!).</string>
	<string name="BROADCAST_PACKAGE_REMOVED">Allows an application to broadcast a notification that an application package has been removed.</string>
	<string name="BROADCAST_SMS">Allows an application to broadcast an SMS receipt notification</string>
	<string name="BROADCAST_STICKY">Allows an application to broadcast sticky intents.</string>
	<string name="BROADCAST_WAP_PUSH">Allows an application to broadcast a WAP PUSH receipt notification</string>
	<string name="CALL_PHONE">Allows an application to initiate a phone call without going through the Dialer user interface for the user to confirm the call being placed.</string>
	<string name="CALL_PRIVILEGED">Allows an application to call any phone number, including emergency numbers, without going through the Dialer user interface for the user to confirm the call being placed.</string>
	<string name="CAMERA">Required to be able to access the camera device.</string>
	<string name="CHANGE_COMPONENT_ENABLED_STATE">Allows an application to change whether an application component (other than its own) is enabled or not.</string>
	<string name="CHANGE_CONFIGURATION">Allows an application to modify the current configuration, such as locale.</string>
	<string name="CHANGE_NETWORK_STATE">Allows applications to change network connectivity state</string>
	<string name="CHANGE_WIFI_MULTICAST_STATE">Allows applications to enter Wi-Fi Multicast mode</string>
	<string name="CHANGE_WIFI_STATE">Allows applications to change Wi-Fi connectivity state</string>
	<string name="CLEAR_APP_CACHE">Allows an application to clear the caches of all installed applications on the device.</string>
	<string name="CLEAR_APP_USER_DATA">Allows an application to clear user data</string>
	<string name="CONTROL_LOCATION_UPDATES">Allows enabling/disabling location update notifications from the radio.</string>
	<string name="DELETE_CACHE_FILES">Allows an application to delete cache files.</string>
	<string name="DELETE_PACKAGES">Allows an application to delete packages.</string>
	<string name="DEVICE_POWER">Allows low-level access to power management</string>
	<string name="DIAGNOSTIC">Allows applications to RW to diagnostic resources.</string>
	<string name="DISABLE_KEYGUARD">Allows applications to disable the keyguard</string>
	<string name="DUMP">Allows an application to retrieve state dump information from system services.</string>
	<string name="EXPAND_STATUS_BAR">Allows an application to expand or collapse the status bar.</string>
	<string name="FACTORY_TEST">Run as a manufacturer test application, running as the root user.</string>
	<string name="FLASHLIGHT">Allows access to the flashlight</string>
	<string name="FORCE_BACK">Allows an application to force a BACK operation on whatever is the top activity.</string>
	<string name="GET_ACCOUNTS">Allows access to the list of accounts in the Accounts Service</string>
	<string name="GET_PACKAGE_SIZE">Allows an application to find out the space used by any package.</string>
	<string name="GET_TASKS">Allows an application to get information about the currently or recently running tasks: a thumbnail representation of the tasks, what activities are running in it, etc.</string>
	<string name="GLOBAL_SEARCH">This permission can be used on content providers to allow the global search system to access their data.</string>
	<string name="HARDWARE_TEST">Allows access to hardware peripherals.</string>
	<string name="INJECT_EVENTS">Allows an application to inject user events (keys, touch, trackball) into the event stream and deliver them to ANY window.</string>
	<string name="INSTALL_LOCATION_PROVIDER">Allows an application to install a location provider into the Location Manager</string>
	<string name="INSTALL_PACKAGES">Allows an application to install packages.</string>
	<string name="INTERNAL_SYSTEM_WINDOW">Allows an application to open windows that are for use by parts of the system user interface.</string>
	<string name="INTERNET">Allows applications to open network sockets.</string>
	<string name="KILL_BACKGROUND_PROCESSES">Allows an application to call killBackgroundProcesses(String).</string>
	<string name="MANAGE_ACCOUNTS">Allows an application to manage the list of accounts in the AccountManager</string>
	<string name="MANAGE_APP_TOKENS">Allows an application to manage (create, destroy, Z-order) application tokens in the window manager.</string>
	<string name="MASTER_CLEAR"></string>
	<string name="MODIFY_AUDIO_SETTINGS">Allows an application to modify global audio settings</string>
	<string name="MODIFY_PHONE_STATE">Allows modification of the telephony state - power on, mmi, etc.</string>
	<string name="MOUNT_FORMAT_FILESYSTEMS">Allows formatting file systems for removable storage.</string>
	<string name="MOUNT_UNMOUNT_FILESYSTEMS">Allows mounting and unmounting file systems for removable storage.</string>
	<string name="NFC">Allows applications to perform I/O operations over NFC </string>
	<string name="PERSISTENT_ACTIVITY">Allow an application to make its activities persistent.</string>
	<string name="PROCESS_OUTGOING_CALLS">Allows an application to monitor, modify, or abort outgoing calls.</string>
	<string name="READ_CALENDAR">Allows an application to read the user\'s calendar data.</string>
	<string name="READ_CALL_LOG">Allows an application to read the user\'s call log.</string>
	<string name="READ_CONTACTS">Allows an application to read the user\'s contacts data.</string>
	<string name="READ_EXTERNAL_STORAGE">Allows an application to read from external storage.</string>
	<string name="READ_FRAME_BUFFER">Allows an application to take screen shots and more generally get access to the frame buffer data</string>
	<string name="READ_HISTORY_BOOKMARKS">Allows an application to read (but not write) the user\'s browsing history and bookmarks.</string>
	<string name="READ_INPUT_STATE">Allows an application to retrieve the current state of keys and switches.</string>
	<string name="READ_LOGS">Allows an application to read the low-level system log files.</string>
	<string name="READ_OWNER_DATA">Allows an application to read the owner\'s data.</string>
	<string name="READ_PHONE_STATE">Allows read only access to phone state.</string>
	<string name="READ_PROFILE">Allows an application to read the user\'s personal profile data.</string>
	<string name="READ_SMS">Allows an application to read SMS messages.</string>
	<string name="READ_SOCIAL_STREAM">Allows an application to read from the user\'s social stream.</string>
	<string name="READ_SYNC_SETTINGS">Allows applications to read the sync settings</string>
	<string name="READ_SYNC_STATS">Allows applications to read the sync stats</string>
	<string name="READ_USER_DICTIONARY">Allows an application to read the user dictionary.</string>
	<string name="REBOOT">Required to be able to reboot the device.</string>
	<string name="RECEIVE_BOOT_COMPLETED">Allows an application to receive the ACTION_BOOT_COMPLETED that is broadcast after the system finishes booting.</string>
	<string name="RECEIVE_MMS">Allows an application to monitor incoming MMS messages, to record or perform processing on them.</string>
	<string name="RECEIVE_SMS">Allows an application to monitor incoming SMS messages, to record or perform processing on them.</string>
	<string name="RECEIVE_WAP_PUSH">Allows an application to monitor incoming WAP push messages.</string>
	<string name="RECORD_AUDIO">Allows an application to record audio</string>
	<string name="REORDER_TASKS">Allows an application to change the Z-order of tasks</string>
	<string name="RESTART_PACKAGES">This constant is deprecated. The restartPackage(String) API is no longer supported. </string>
	<string name="SEND_SMS">Allows an application to send SMS messages.</string>
	<string name="SET_ACTIVITY_WATCHER">Allows an application to watch and control how activities are started globally in the system.</string>
	<string name="SET_ALARM">Allows an application to broadcast an Intent to set an alarm for the user.</string>
	<string name="SET_ALWAYS_FINISH">Allows an application to control whether activities are immediately finished when put in the background.</string>
	<string name="SET_ANIMATION_SCALE">Modify the global animation scaling factor.</string>
	<string name="SET_DEBUG_APP">Configure an application for debugging.</string>
	<string name="SET_ORIENTATION">Allows low-level access to setting the orientation (actually rotation) of the screen.</string>
	<string name="SET_POINTER_SPEED">Allows low-level access to setting the pointer speed.</string>
	<string name="SET_PREFERRED_APPLICATIONS">This constant is deprecated. No longer useful, see addPackageToPreferred(String) for details. </string>
	<string name="SET_PROCESS_LIMIT">Allows an application to set the maximum number of (not needed) application processes that can be running.</string>
	<string name="SET_TIME">Allows applications to set the system time</string>
	<string name="SET_TIME_ZONE">Allows applications to set the system time zone</string>
	<string name="SET_WALLPAPER">Allows applications to set the wallpaper</string>
	<string name="SET_WALLPAPER_HINTS">Allows applications to set the wallpaper hints</string>
	<string name="SIGNAL_PERSISTENT_PROCESSES">Allow an application to request that a signal be sent to all persistent processes</string>
	<string name="STATUS_BAR">Allows an application to open, close, or disable the status bar and its icons.</string>
	<string name="SUBSCRIBED_FEEDS_READ">Allows an application to allow access the subscribed feeds ContentProvider.</string>
	<string name="SUBSCRIBED_FEEDS_WRITE"></string>
	<string name="SYSTEM_ALERT_WINDOW">Allows an application to open windows using the type TYPE_SYSTEM_ALERT, shown on top of all other applications.</string>
	<string name="UPDATE_DEVICE_STATS">Allows an application to update device statistics.</string>
	<string name="USE_CREDENTIALS">Allows an application to request authtokens from the AccountManager</string>
	<string name="USE_SIP">Allows an application to use SIP service </string>
	<string name="VIBRATE">Allows access to the vibrator</string>
	<string name="WAKE_LOCK">Allows using PowerManager WakeLocks to keep processor from sleeping or screen from dimming</string>
	<string name="WRITE_APN_SETTINGS">Allows applications to write the apn settings</string>
	<string name="WRITE_CALENDAR">Allows an application to write (but not read) the user\'s calendar data.</string>
	<string name="WRITE_CALL_LOG">Allows an application to write (but not read) the user\'s contacts data.</string>
	<string name="WRITE_CONTACTS">Allows an application to write (but not read) the user\'s contacts data.</string>
	<string name="WRITE_EXTERNAL_STORAGE">Allows an application to write to external storage</string>
	<string name="WRITE_GSERVICES">Allows an application to modify the Google service map.</string>
	<string name="WRITE_HISTORY_BOOKMARKS">Allows an application to write (but not read) the user\'s browsing history and bookmarks.</string>
	<string name="WRITE_OWNER_DATA">Allows an application to write (but not read) the owner\'s data.</string>
	<string name="WRITE_PROFILE">Allows an application to write (but not read) the user\'s personal profile data.</string>
	<string name="WRITE_SECURE_SETTINGS">Allows an application to read or write the secure system settings.</string>
	<string name="WRITE_SETTINGS">Allows an application to read or write the system settings.</string>
	<string name="WRITE_SMS">Allows an application to write SMS messages.</string>
	<string name="WRITE_SOCIAL_STREAM">Allows an application to write (but not read) the user\'s social stream data.</string>
	<string name="WRITE_SYNC_SETTINGS">Allows applications to write the sync settings</string>
	<string name="WRITE_USER_DICTIONARY">Allows an application to write to the user dictionary.</string>
</resources>